I'm so excited for the dodgeball game
tomorrow. It's my most favorite part of
summer camp. What about you, Astro?
>> Oh,
uh, me, too.
>> You better be ready, Astro, cuz the red
team's coming for those cute little
booty cheeks of yours.
>> Yeah, they'll be ready.
>> Unfortunately, because we got that
popped tire on the bus, we arrived at
the campsite later than expected, so
everyone needs to head straight to the
cabins and get ready for bed.
Shut up. All of you, shut up. We are
going to have a fun weekend, or half of
you are going to wind up in the dirt.
Red shirts are sleeping in the cabin on
the left, and blue shirts go on the
right. The team leaders are me and
Sprout, but don't come to us for
anything. If you are being bullied, or
have something you just got to talk
about in private, go talk to one of the
assigned camp counselors for the
weekend, Dial, Sylvester, or Miss
Teagan. They're the [__] dressed like
big bananas.
>> Dost thou hear, sexy pumpkin? Should any
burden weigh upon thy mind, no matter
how small, my cabin door is always open.
You know who to talk to, preferably
one-on-one.
>> Hee hee, oopsie, Poppy did a poopsie.
>> It was like just the bed. It's old,
obviously.
>> You're so funny, Poppy. You're giving us
all the giggles.
>> Haha, I am, aren't I?
>> It was just the chair, right?
I'm the top farter in Garden View, so
don't step up on me at my own game,
[__]
>> Scraps, you seeing this, fairy [__]
>> Woah, easy there, Tinkerbell.
>> Don't turn to your friend for help,
[__] Farting up a storm is my thing,
Poppy. It's how I assert dominance up in
this [__]
>> I'm like "Going to tell the counselors
you're bullying me."
>> Try it, girlfriend, and I'll just tell
them you're discriminating against me
for being gay. They won't listen to you.
You're not that [__] I'm that [__]
Blue dorm.
>> I know we just got here, but it's late.
Lights out. We've got a big day of
summer camp tomorrow. There's the
friendship bracelet event, the dodgeball
event, and there's
>> Come tuck me in, Dial. I'm not paying
you for nothing.
>> Hey, Danny. Can I come over to your bed?
>> Yeah.
What's wrong?
>> I'm just scared about the dodgeball game
tomorrow.
>> Why? You got four arms, which means you
can throw like four balls at the same
time.
>> That's true, but you know, I don't like
violence. And even more than hurting
others, I don't want to be the one
getting hurt.
>> You'll be fine cuz I'll protect you.
What? I'm super strong for a cute little
flower.
>> Sorry, it's just this is kind of gay.
Two boys sharing a bed like this at
summer camp.
>> Yeah, it would look that way to others.
Maybe you should get out.
Or if you want to keep laying here,
that's fine, too. What are best friends
if we can't share a bed without it being
weird. Just as long as you're out before
anyone else wakes up.
>> Hey, can I hug you with all four of my
arms just like I used to do when we were
first becoming friends?
>> We did used to sleep that way a lot.
>> Cosmo, these taters represent but a
small portion of my potato treasury. If
thou throws the dodgeball game for the
blue team this evening, there's more
taters where that comes from.
>> What?
Oh, Sylvester, I know you Halloween
toons stick together, but you can't
expect me to throw the game just to make
Gordie happy.
>> Then half the smash taters return to my
keeping. Be on thy way.
>> Haha Sprout, you made me drop my mashed
potatoes. Yeah, they're all over my
little toesies now. I won't wash them,
so you can lick it off later.
I saw you talking to Sylvester. Was he
picking on you? A cute little thing like
you needs protection. Sprout, we're
always together anyway. You don't have
to act tough. You're going to do your
best strawberry friend good at the
dodgeball game this evening, right? Why
wouldn't I? Got to make you look good.
That's what I like to hear. Don't go
letting anyone else around here try to
say you ain't a good little [__] You
been preparing? A little. I'm just
scared about being hit. Come on now. You
of all toons shouldn't be scared about
having balls flying towards his face
from every which way.
>> Oopsie, Poppy did a poopsie.
>> [screaming]
>> Roger, look. I'm making friendship
bracelets. I want you to have this one.
>> I thought that one was meant for me.
>> Oh, Sylvester, you can't have all the
ones I make.
>> Fine, but I do not take kindly to seeing
you hand gifts out like a common harlot.
>> Gordie, if you're trying to make a
rainbow, then you need to switch the L
and the P. Orange is supposed to be
between the red and the yellow.
>> Why isn't it opening?
Dandy, you were in there? I didn't even
hear you. Yeah? I was peeing. Wait,
don't tell me you're one of those
[__] who pees on the side of the bowl
because you're insecure about tunes
outside the bathroom hearing you. Who
cares where I do it? Well, I pee
directly into the water so that it's as
loud as possible to assert dominance.
Glad that works out for you, Seedling.
Hey, boys. Me and Dandy are trying to
settle a debate. When you're peeing out
of your balls, where do you aim in the
bowl?
>> Pee in the water and poop on the side of
the bowl.
>> See, Dandy? That's what I'm talking
about. Wait, what?
>> I poop on the side of the bowl and pee
in the water.
>> That's horrible.
>> Well, you don't want to cut a turd, have
it fall in the water, and have the poopy
water splash back up and hit your butt.
>> How big are your poops that happens to
you, Roger?
>> No, I just told you I poop on the side
of the bowl so it doesn't happen.
>> Astro, where do you pee?
>> Directly into the water. It makes sure I
don't miss. I only miss sometimes. Look,
Sylvester is bringing out the
dodgeballs.
>> I love balls.
>> So, team, you ready to kick some serious
strawberry butt this year?
>> With you as our team leader again this
year, we're so ready.
>> Yeah, it's thanks to you, Dandy, that
the blue team has won the summer camp
dodgeball game for 10 years in a row.
>> Well, they're not wrong. Dandy knows his
way around some dodgeballs.
>> Dandy is really good at anything that
has to do with dodgeballs. The bigger
the dodgeballs, the better for him, I
bet.
>> Yeah, Dandy is really good at gripping
dodgeballs.
>> For claiming to be straight, you got to
wonder how Dandy got so experienced with
dodgeballs.
>> Hey, Dandy. I want to show you something
by the trash cans real quick. I don't
want to. That sounds smelly. Just come
look, you dweeb. It's something cool.
Oh, boy. I love cool things. I don't see
anything. No, you got to look a bit
deeper.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING? LET ME out of
this thing. No can do, dork. I'm going
to wreck your stupid win streak, no
matter what it takes. Help me.
Who's ready for the dodgeball game? What
are you all staring at?
Well, the good news is they're too
muscular to throw accurately, right?
Hey, has anyone seen Dandy? How are we
supposed to play without our team
captain?
Oopsie, Poppy did a poopsie. Okay,
[__] We get it. It was funny the first
two times. Why does Poppy keep doing
that? I think she's trying to make it
her catchphrase. For what purpose? All
it does is makes it sound like she
crapped herself.
We just got word that Dandy has yet to
show up for the dodgeball game. If he
does not show up within 5 minutes, we
regret to inform you all that the red
team will win by forfeit.
Damn, that sucks. But rules are rules.
This is awful. Where is that flower?
Dandy will show up. Just you wait.
What do you want, Cosmo? I I heard you
guys were looking for Dandy. I think I
saw where he went, but I don't want
Sprout to be mad at me.
What do you dorks want? Sprout, can we
please look inside the red team's cabin?
You trying to accuse me of something
nefarious? Perhaps.
Listen, Dandy told me he was going home
cuz he sucked at dodgeball. That's all I
know. That doesn't sound like him at
all. Well, it's what happened, so leave.
Nobody is allowed in the red cabin until
after the dodgeball game is over. You
hear me? And you, you think you're being
cute by being buddy-buddy with the
enemy, Cosmo? GET IN HERE.
ASTRO, HURRY INSIDE before Sprout hits
me again.
Why is the attic door open?
I tried asking Sprout that and he hit
me, gave me a black eye, spit in my
mouth, called me his slave, and then
told me to mind my own business.
Astro.
Dandy, your petals, they're gone. Who
did this to you? Sprout did. Are you
stupid? Oh my god. There's no god here
today. I bet you were in on this, too.
Weren't you? You cosmic brownie [__]
Golly, I wasn't. I swear. Cosmo helped
me look for you.
Why do you smell like pee? The
strawberry peed on me. What do you
think? He did it to hide my scent from
you toons.
Wait, two Dandys? How is this possible?
No, that's not me. That's Sprout. What
are you talking about, Sprout? I'm
Dandy. Dandy, the funny little flower.
The son of a [__] is trying to steal my
life cuz he's jealous of how cool and
sexy I am. Astro, you're a pretty cool
toon. You've always been my best friend,
so I'm going to give you one more chance
to climb out of this attic and pretend
like you didn't see anything up in this
[__] No, you're not my best friend.
Dandy is. But I am Dandy. No, this is my
Dandy and I'm not going to let you STEAL
HIS LIFE.
>> [screaming]
>> ASTRO, ARE YOU OKAY?
WHO'S that toon you're holding? It looks
kind of like Dandy, but it's obviously
not him because Dandy has petals and
this [__] doesn't.
>> Look, there's Dandy right there.
>> I order all of you to take Sprout away
and throw him off a cliff.
>> No, don't listen to him, besties. This
is Dandy. That one is Sprout.
>> You'll never get away with this, Sprout.
The town of Gardenview will never be
yours. These toons are smarter than this
and more than their surprisingly high
IQs, they're my friends.
>> Lolly, hold on there. Tegan, put down
the gun.
>> Shoot him, Tegan. I'm the real Dandy.
Sprout is trying to lie to you.
>> What? No, he's the one lying. Shoot him.
>> I can't tell. They look identical.
>> We need to ask them something only the
real Dandy would know. What color are
Dandy's petals?
>> Uh, well, I know they like look like the
gay FLAG OR SOMETHING.
>> YAY!
>> [cheering and screaming]
>> YAY, WE SHOT SPROUT.
>> What's going on here? Tegan, did you
shoot another camper? This is 3 years in
a row now.
>> A toon was shot?
>> Who?
>> It was my poor Dandy.
>> Actually, Astro, that's Sprout who was
shot. Dandy is the one over there with
the petals on his head. We've just been
through this.
>> Does this mean the red team won or not?
>> Rather, I would have to say the annual
dodgeball game will have to be canceled
this year.
>> Oh my god, Dandy was Sprout all along.
>> What can I say, team? I I just wanted to
win. I was tired of losing to Dandy
every goddamn year.
>> No, Sprout, you're wrong. This game is
still on and it's going to be on till
the day I die.
>> Dandy, don't force yourself to be a
strong little flower. You can barely
even stand.
>> I will go into battle as a [__] if I
have to. I don't care. If Sprout was so
impressed with my life that he would go
and try to steal it, well, then I'm
going to make him even more jealous of
it by claiming victory over a stupid
little game like dodgeball. You hear
that, Sprout? The challenge is still on
and I'm taking everything from you. I
won't stop until I've made your whole
life hell. I'm going to kick your ass
out there on the field, get that trophy,
and then just to dig the knife even
further, I'm going to claim your little
[__] boy Cosmo's body for myself.
>> [music]
[music]
>> When I count to three, [music] the game
will begin immediately. Everyone on both
sides will rush towards the center of
the [music] field and grab their balls.
We're playing street rules where one hit
and you're out. The match will keep
going until every member of one team is
completely wiped out [music] and the
other team wins. 1 2 3 begin.
>> They got [music] to the dodgeballs
first. Everybody fall back.
>> [screaming]
>> Aim for the kneecaps. If [music] we
break their legs, they can't run away.
>> Poppy, get your fat cheeks up. We can
still save you.
>> I'm already out. You got to like knee
me, girl.
>> [music]
>> Shrimper, because Finn caught your ball,
that means you're out by default.
>> What?
>> Because Finn has drowned in the lake,
Finn has also been disqualified. The
blue team is [music] down to five
players, while the red team still has an
impressive nine.
>> Everyone aim for Gordie. Child tunes
[music] can't run that fast, so he makes
for an easy target.
Dang it, Roger.
>> [music]
>> Heck yeah, there's a two-for-one special
for you. Get off the field, you dorks.
[music]
What? No, you hit my wheelchair. That
doesn't count. Well, why not? You need
it to move around with, so it's part of
your person. Yeah, but it's not
literally me. Okay, well then, does that
mean Roger didn't get out either cuz it
hit his shirt and not his face? That's
different and you know it. Dial.
We're going to give this a pass, Dandy,
but if your wheelchair gets hit again,
Dandy, you're out. Damn Dial, you can't
still be that bitter that I broke up
with you on your birthday. It's been 2
years, let it go. You don't have any say
in how long I can hold on to things,
Dandicus. Whatever. You heard him,
Circus Trio, aim for the wheelchair. If
I can trust anyone to take down a
[__] it's other mentally crippled
clowns.
I'm not against HITTING CRIPPLES,
EITHER.
>> [screaming]
[screaming]
>> AND JUST LIKE THAT, Louie Yato Toodles
and Blot are out of the game. See,
Astro? I told you there's nothing to
worry about when it comes to dodgeball,
not for someone like you.
Where is everybody? Wait, am I the only
one left? Hold on, I got to encourage my
boy.
Cosmo, Cosmo, you can do it. I know you
were scared about this whole dodgeball
thing, but now it's time to prove
yourself. It's just Astro and a crippled
flower out there now. You can do it.
>> [screaming]
>> What's he doing? Cosmo, I know you're
not running away. There's no running in
dodgeball.
Astro.
Wait, if it wasn't for me, your team
would have been disqualified. Oh, come
on, Cosmo. You're making yourself look
like a little [__] Don't do this.
Please, let me have this. Let my whole
team have this.
Dandy, our team does win every single
year. Maybe it wouldn't hurt to be nice
and give them a trophy just once. It
would be nice.
But nobody has ever known Dandicus
Danceifer to be nice.
Diva down.
I told you Dandy wasn't going to hold
back. He's got that pent-up manlet rage.
>> [laughter]
>> Cosmo, we can blow this whole trip and
go home if your side hurts that bad. No,
it's just that I ruined all of summer
camp for you.
Hey, you didn't do that. All you cared
about was winning the dodgeball game,
and I didn't do diddly squat. I just
cowered the whole time. I looked like a
little [__] out there. I'm a bad
friend. No, you're my best friend. I
care more about the fun we had together
today anyway. But we didn't even do
anything fun together, either. I brought
you an ice pack, so let's get that shirt
off of you and put this on. Well, okay.
I always have trouble because of my big
head.
Let me help you with that, CREAM PUFF.
>> DAMN, BOY, HE THICK. BOY,
THAT'S A THICK ASS BOY. DAMN.
>> [clears throat]
>> DID I GET HIM?
>> [screaming]
>> COSMO SUCKS. Cosmo sucks. Cosmo sucks.
Cosmo sucks. Cosmo sucks.
>> I want to take you someplace private.
Let's go.
>> Where are you taking me, Dandy?
>> This is going to sound like a weird
question, but how flexible are you
feeling right now?
>> Oh, that is a weird question. Moderately
flexible, I suppose, but I'd say it
depends on the reason you're asking.
>> You'll see.
>> What are we doing back here?
>> Wait right here a bit, and you'll find
out.
>> Sprout, don't push me so hard. My side
still hurts. We're trying to get some
alone time, aren't we? The red team will
be back in this cabin any minute.
>> Hurry up, slowpoke.
>> Haha. Well, if you want me to go any
faster, then you shouldn't be
distracting me with such a fat butt in
my face.
>> Dandy?
>> Woah. Has Dandy always been this freaky?
He seems taller than usual. Maybe that's
why he wanted to do this in the dark. I
bet he's on a stepping stool. That's so
cute.
>> Cosmo's head feels rounder than usual,
or maybe I'm just imagining things, but
I don't care. I've been waiting all
weekend for this.
>> Cosmo, what are you doing here?
>> This is the red team's cabin. I'm just
here with Sprout. He's in the attic.
>> Uh, no. I was just up there. Astro's the
one in the attic.
>> Good golly, we just put two gay tunes
together.
>> Dial said, "We'll be home in 10 minutes.
You and me are getting off at the first
stop, so we'll be home faster than all
the others. That'll be nice, right?"
I'm sorry about what happened in the
attic.
>> It's fine. It was dark. You couldn't see
a thing. Why would I care about what you
do with other toons, especially boy
toons? I'm not gay.
>> Uh-huh. Are you sure about that?
Sorry.
Thanks for walking me home, Andy. Do you
want to come inside?
>> Why would I want to do that?
>> So we can talk about what happened at
summer camp.
>> I already said I don't care.
Fine.
I don't like that strawberry stink on
you.
>> Oh, um I'll go take a shower then.
>> [music]
>> What are you doing?
>> No. No, don't. I don't want to do that
right now.
>> It's been a month since our last icker
extraction.
>> You said it could wait until after
summer camp.
>> Yeah. Isn't it after summer camp now?
>> You were more rough that time than
usual.
So you
are mad at me.
>> Go take a shower, you filthy thing.
Hey there, cute viewer. I just got done
peeing directly into the water in the
toilet. Because you're cool as heck, I'm
going to let you in on a little secret.
Did you know there's a special episode
of Dandy's World that was taken down by
YouTube because it was too sexy? It's
called Dandy's World Finn goes twisted.
If you go over to Tamers12345's
Patreon right now and subscribe, you can
check it out right now. You'll also find
a ton of other cool things like gifts
from this episode and all the ones used
in past Dandy's World episodes.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Running in the sand,
living on [music] the land.
The salty breeze was in our eyes. We
[music and singing] stood beneath the
dragonflies and danced
>> [music]
>> all
night. [music]
We polished [music] all the chrome
on a rusty little home.
We slept [music] all night in parking
lots. We tied our hearts in double knots
so tight.
So free,
so [music]
bright.
Remember
when
we were just cherubs [music] in our
tender [singing]
skins,
waiting [music] patiently for love
>> [singing]
>> to begin.
Flowing [music] so free,
blowing in the breeze. [singing]
The songs [music] we sung so long ago,
with whiskey and [singing] an afterglow,
we shined
>> [music]
>> like
new.
>> [music]
>> But there along the way,
some things changed.
As weeks [music] turned into months, we
knew as life caught up, we slowly grew
apart.
And
>> [music]
>> untied
our
hearts.
Remember
when
we were just cherishing our
tender skins,
>> [music]
>> waiting patiently for life
>> to begin.
But the summer went away [music] and the
stars went gray.
We slowly ran
out of things to say. The river turned
into drought and
time was fading out.
>> [music]
>> Defeated and alone, we returned back
home like a bird without a wing who
would never fly away
into a
suspended dream.
>> [music]
>> Remember [music]
when
you walked away in the
December [music]
wind,
I felt the stinging on my [music] pale
skin.
I knew that things would never be
[music] the same you again.
Remember
when
the clouds [music] rolled in
and then the
sunlight
dimmed out.
>> [music]
>> And what will be blacked out will burn.
>> Burn.
>> [music]
[music]
>> We have arrived at the last stop,
Gordie. Time for you to get off.
>> Uh, are you sure this is the right stop?
It looks more like the middle of
nowhere.
>> You can walk home. It's only a short
journey away.
>> Not really. We're like 67 mi away from
my house.
I'm just going to go then.
>> Would you have me escort you home? A
lovely thing such as yourself deserves a
knight's protection.
>> Uh, that's okay. I'm good.